Hello everyone, welcome back to to this another tutorial topic. So today here I can just going to explore for how to insert data in the MongoDB collections.
Inserting data in MongoDB is the fundamental operation that allows us to add new document to the collection, okay.
So first of all here inserting data into the MongoDB collection can be done. It is in for the insert on many methods to the MongoDB.
And you can choose for here the MongoDB shell and now you can create for the MongoDB.
Use the MongoDB campus and now here choose for the database for.
The test episode now I can just select and here.
I can just go for click on this data and now here at for this data, okay. So now.
I can just choose for this pattern. So now choose for the info projection file of the CSV file and now go for the insert document, okay.
So here I can just use this on.
And I'm going to use this one and click for this icon and also click for here at the screen up for the file, okay.
Now just go here and simply create for the name.
Okay, so the name then go for here the name of the MongoDB, okay.
So the MongoDB is perfectly created now and here simply created and here completely simple and this is the own data, okay.
So this now insert one and then just click for this insert button and you can see here perfectly created this MongoDB is the insert for your own data, okay.
So this is completely in your system now here. I can just give it for the one more data. So I can again press for at data and now I can go here the insert document and now.
I'm going to paste for this document and here press for the class icon and also for the account key and here first of all, I can type the receiving name, okay.
So the name insert for the name is supposed like this tab last name, okay.
And now just go for again the field so I can use for another field.
So here I can just use for this is the age and now I can define for the ages.
And also for at another column so now I can just press for the ad and here I can create is the email and here insert for the email is supposed like the Johan at the right gmail.com, okay.
So now here completely defined for here and use for many data is defined for the multiple documents so now.
So now it is completely created and here I can dispute for the insert button and you can see here perfectly created for the two tables of first thing the name only the MongoDB and here insert for the name is the name, okay.
So here completely use for now, here I can use for another statement so now I can dispute for inserting document with the customer side, okay.
So now just go here and use the style inside the document and simplest the class point is 45 and still first of all the ID ID is already created here so here simply use for the name.
So the name is called the product, okay.
So this is the product called, okay, okay.
And here use for and now here I can add for another column.
So now here I can dispute for the plastic on and also go here at the time this is the price, okay.
And now here I can insert for the data so now I can use for the price is 15, okay.
So now here simply define for this and we can simply store while the insert data, okay.
And eventually we want the perfect data, the three data, three table information so here perfectly applied for the insert one or inserting document or the last one, okay.
So these are great for simply for the random details also implement for the customers IP and here use the new reason and second of price, okay.
So here in this session is completely done and here I can perfectly overview the inserting data into the MongoDB collection of some practical example, okay.
So I hope you can understand this simple process so thank you for watching and happy data coding, okay.